http://tarotmania.co.uk/privacy-policy.htm

How to Give Tarot Card Readings
Are Tarot Cards a Game?
Sitemap Page
Tarot Mania Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy oversees the manner in which Tarot Mania gathers, uses, preserves and discloses information collected from our users. This privacy policy is relevant to the site as well as all services and products rendered by Tarot Mania.
Personal identification informationIn order to use Tarot Mania's website, we may collect personal identification information from visitors in a several of ways. Users may be asked to provide us with their name and email address to enlist in our online tarot course to learn about the best tarot cards for beginners and more. We will only collect the above information if the visitor voluntarily submits such information to us. If the visitor turns down to provide personal identification information, it might prevent them from participating in certain site-related activities.Changes to this privacy policyTarot Mani has the discretion to adjusts this privacy at any time.
We advise that you inspect it regularly to observe any changes that have been made. You accept and understand that it is your duty to go over this privacy policy from time to time to become aware of changes. If you have any questions, remarks or concerns, visit our contact us page and get in touch.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this site, you accept this policy and its terms of service.
If you do not approve of this policy, please do not use Tarot Mania's site.
Your continued use of our site, along with the posting changes to this privacy policy will be regarded as your acceptance of those changes.
